{
  "Request_ID": "4225e56e-4b68-4372-9d34-66bba1a633b3",
  "Timestamp": "2022-03-11T12:09:43.5122616+00:00",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "Question_Id": "452d7766-aeed-488c-9fc3-06f378bbfb30",
      "Question": "Do you want slicing?",
      "IsSingleAnswer": true,
      "Answer": [ { "key": true } ],
      "Timestamp": "2022-03-11T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
    },
    {
      "Question_Id": "452d7946-aeed-488c-9fc3-06f378bbfb30",
      "Question": "Do you have a map?",
      "IsSingleAnswer": true,
      "Answer": [ { "key": true } ],
      "Timestamp": "2022-03-11T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
    },
    {
      "Question_Id": "12d8df44-0027-4d2c-809d-7d4018d3adc6",
      "Question": "How many maps do you have?",
      "IsSingleAnswer": true,
      "Answer": [ { "key": 2 } ],
      "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
    },

    {
      "Question_Id": "46e3662a-f94c-4770-8a5a-ef3ba4e49122",
      "Question": "What types of maps do you have?",
      "IsSingleAnswer": false,
      "Answer": [
        { "2ac61d8b-896d-4428-867b-d3483bcb5c88": "2d_Geometry" },
        {
          "4dd2464f-0215-4bd5-9f2f-07c32f1f5eaa": 
          "2d_Semantic"
        }
      ],
      "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
    },

    {
      "Question_Id": "bc004162-8e24-45cf-807a-4a0cfe4082fc",
      "Question": "How much do you trust each map?",
      "IsSingleAnswer": false,
      "Answer": [
        { "2ac61d8b-896d-4428-867b-d3483bcb5c88": 90 },
        {
          "4dd2464f-0215-4bd5-9f2f-07c32f1f5eaa":25
        }
      ],
      "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
    },

    {
      "Question_Id": "e2b78764-61bd-425b-a39b-b11fdc96ac04",
      "Question": "Do you know your possition in the maps?",
      "IsSingleAnswer": false,
      "Answer": [
        { "2ac61d8b-896d-4428-867b-d3483bcb5c88": true },
        { "4dd2464f-0215-4bd5-9f2f-07c32f1f5eaa": "N/A" }
      ],
      "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
      },

        {
          "Question_Id": "4a738ff9-a8e3-4105-8ac2-8900dd6df621",
          "Question": "Are you doing the task alone?",
          "IsSingleAnswer": true,
          "Answer": [ { "key": true } ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-09T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        },

        {
          "Question_Id": "0c41615a-5b32-43c4-a56e-2ef1a5282625",
          "Question": "How critical are the tasks for you?",
          "IsSingleAnswer": true,
          "Answer": [ { "key": "High" } ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        },

        {
          "Question_Id": "45ca9062-d97c-411d-aea1-142a552d701e",
          "Question": "How dangerous is this task?",
          "IsSingleAnswer": true,
          "Answer": [ { "key": "Low" } ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        },

        {
          "Question_Id": "c680514a-62c7-46d2-aaa9-89ea8d393b03",
          "Question": "The tasks to perform will be done in a local close space?",
          "IsSingleAnswer": true,
          "Answer": [ { "key": true } ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        },

        {
          "Question_Id": "502d4c13-8a00-4466-8262-b1a8bcc10dea",
          "Question": "What is your wireless internet speed?",
          "IsSingleAnswer": false,
          "Answer": [
            { "upload": 90 },
            { "download": 100 },
            { "latency": 100 }
          ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        },

        {
          "Question_Id": "c2911b70-4f15-4be4-8f48-a870baecd866",
          "Question": "Will you carry or use dangerous objects",
          "IsSingleAnswer": true,
          "Answer": [ { "key": false } ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        },

        {
          "Question_Id": "b60c8e4b-bbe3-49e8-b8f6-8fc920d05f46",
          "Question": "Do you have a time limit to perform the task, specify amount in minutes",
          "IsSingleAnswer": true,
          "Answer": [ { "key": 60 } ],
          "Timestamp": "2022-03-10T12:09:43.5122616+00:00"
        }
      ]

 }
